copper?
どう?
Was it interesting?
面白かった?
What?
何が?
The blood is disgusting...
血が気持ち悪い...
nice.
いいね
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみて
Why are you hiding it?
なんで隠してるの?
Dude, what is it?
おいさん、なんだ?
It's all the way to the back.
後ろまでだし
Shall we take a shower together?
一緒にシャワー浴びるか
Hey?
ねえ?
It feels good to be hidden.
隠してる感じがいいよね
Let's go, then take a shower.
行こう、じゃあシャワー
I guess I'll take a shower then.
じゃあシャワー浴びようかね
Isn't it hot?
熱くない?
this.
これ
It was so hot.
こんなに暑かったんだね
It was really exciting.
本当にうるんだったね
Oh, that's terrible.
あー、やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
In your mouth...
口にさ...
Can I take out a lot?
いっぱい出していい?
Is it okay?
いい の?
Ah, let's go?
あー、いくよ?
Oh, it spilled.
あ、こぼれちゃったね
Down below.
下にね
Do you want to taste more and more?
どんどん味する?
delicious?
おいしい?
We had sex, a lot.
エッチしたね、いっぱい
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Let's try again.
もう一回しようよ
Let's take off the top
上を脱いでみよう
mosquito.
か
Did you stand up on a chair?
椅 子立ちになったかな?
Wow, that's it.
すごい、そうやって
Can I take it back?
裏取っちゃっていい?
what happened?
どうしたの?
You look erotic.
エロい顔してるな
Shall I take off my bottom too?
下も脱いちゃうか
It's so beautiful.
すっごいきれいだね
Could you open your legs a little?
足ちょっと開いてごらん?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Why don't you open it yourself?
自分で開いてごらん?
Good luck
うまくい
like this.
こう
It seems so.
や らしいね
Would you like to open it again yourself?
もう一回自分で開いてごらん?
Show me clearly.
しっかり見せて
It comes with something like a tissue.
ティッシュみたいなのがついてる
Please open it firmly.
しっかり開いてごらん?
It's so erotic.
すごいエロいし
Would you please take off your pants?
パンツ脱がしてごらん?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I can't stand it.
我慢できないよ
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
copper?
どう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's really tight.
すっごいきつい
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad.
やばい、やばい、やばい
Poop?
うんち?
amazing.
すごい